<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2016-11-21T21:24:20+00:00</updated><id>https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org//</id><subtitle>We can change the future of America, but we need your help.</subtitle><author><name>{&quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;&quot;@OurPoliticalRev&quot;}</name></author><entry><title type="html">Bernie Sanders to Speak at Rally in Washington DC</title><link href="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/16/bernie-sanders-to-speak-at-rally-in-washington-dc.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bernie Sanders to Speak at Rally in Washington DC" /><published>2016-11-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-11-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/16/bernie-sanders-to-speak-at-rally-in-washington-dc</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/16/bernie-sanders-to-speak-at-rally-in-washington-dc.html">&lt;p&gt;Bernie Sanders will make his first rally appearance since the election, taking the stage on Thursday, November 17th in Washington DC. The rally, sponsored by National Nurses United and with support from Progressive Democrats for America, aims to promote a progressive agenda and a common commitment to social and economic justice and equality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/thepoliticalrev.org/assets/images/posts/rally_for_soc_econ_equal_just_1024.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The revolution has spread its wings. Rally for Social and Economic Justice and Inequality&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rally is in direct response to the incoming Trump administration, bringing Progressives together to discuss 
concerns including job creation, climate action, the recent escalation of hate-related violence, and the de facto 
defeat of the Trans-Pacific Partnership. Participate in this day of action to help forward the progressive initiative. 
Stop Speaker Ryan from privatizing Medicare, and defend the hard earned rights of Labor in the United States. Hear 
those that are fighting for a Political Revolution, and in turn make your voice heard!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other groups in support of the rally include: National Nurses United, Our Revolution, AFL-CIO, Communications Workers of 
America, Demand Progress, The People For Bernie Sanders, Amalgamated Transit Union, Transport Workers Union, Working 
Families Party, Democratic Socialists of America, Democracy Spring, The American Postal Workers Union, People’s Action, 
Social Security Works, Progressive Democrats of America, Public Citizen, Health GAP.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what&quot;&gt;What&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rally for Social and Economic Justice and Equality&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Featured Speaker – Sen. Bernie Sanders&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;when&quot;&gt;When&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thursday, November 17, 1 p.m.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;where&quot;&gt;Where&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Upper Senate Park, U.S. Capitol, Washington DC&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://go.ourrevolution.com/page/event/detail/volunteeractivityormeeting/gplgcf&quot;&gt;Our Revolution&lt;/a&gt; is providing free round trip transportation to the rally from &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/forms/dr3OfqAj8YfGxU5f1&quot;&gt;Brooklyn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/forms/7b7QasyATyRuSMA33&quot;&gt;Manhattan&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://goo.gl/forms/UtjWSynXznuEbVl93&quot;&gt;Philadelphia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Vienna Thompkins</name></author><summary type="html">Bernie Sanders will make his first rally appearance since the election, taking the stage on Thursday, November 17th in Washington DC. The rally, sponsored by National Nurses United and with support from Progressive Democrats for America, aims to promote a progressive agenda and a common commitment to social and economic justice and equality.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/assets/images/bernie-rally.png" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Rise Up in Solidarity for National Day of Action Against The Dakota Access Pipeline</title><link href="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/14/dapl-day-of-action.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Rise Up in Solidarity for National Day of Action Against The Dakota Access Pipeline" /><published>2016-11-14T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-11-14T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/14/dapl-day-of-action</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/14/dapl-day-of-action.html">&lt;p&gt;The ongoing protest against the construction of the Dakota Access Pipeline (DAPL) has generated a great deal of press over the past few months. This Tuesday, November 15th, we, the outraged of the United States will demonstrate our &lt;a href=&quot;https://actionnetwork.org/event_campaigns/nov-15-nodapl-day-of-action-at-army-corps-of-engineers&quot;&gt;nationwide solidarity&lt;/a&gt; with the people of the Standing Rock Sioux Tribe in opposition to this project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Running from the Bakken oil fields in western North Dakota to southern Illinois, the proposed pipeline would cross beneath the Missouri and Mississippi rivers, as well as part of Lake Oahe near the Standing Rock Indian Reservation. Opposition to the project raised by Indigenous nations, farmers, landowners, and conservation groups has focused on the potential for significant damage to the environment, both during construction and as an ongoing risk once the pipeline is operational. DAPL risks endangering a source of fresh water for the Standing Rock Sioux and 8 million people living downstream. DAPL would also impact many sites that are sacred to the Standing Rock Sioux and other Indigenous nations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/thepoliticalrev.org/assets/images/posts/dapl-flower.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Crowd of peaceful protestors at the demonstration against DAPL&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The reaction of the authorities to these concerns has been both dismissive and heavy-handed. North Dakota state troopers, the National Guard, other law enforcement agencies, and private security firms have meted out harsh treatment on protesters, utilizing attack dogs and pepper spray alongside arrests and strip-searches in their attempt to break the people’s opposition to the construction of the pipeline.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a call to action for those who care about the rights of Indigenous people to land, about the right to peaceful protest without violent repression, and about protecting our natural environment on which we rely for life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NOW&lt;/strong&gt; is the time to act. We have an opportunity to be part of a movement that says &lt;strong&gt;NO&lt;/strong&gt; to corporate greed, violent raids by police, and complacent government.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will  congregate at the offices of the US Army Corps of Engineers - the body that issued the planning permits and failed to consider the catastrophic environmental damage to land and water.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/maps/d/viewer?mid=1No5ksK9HNGmvwyLYPbJAYuuK9H0&amp;amp;ll=17.182552304096777,-84.51124379999999&amp;amp;z=2&quot;&gt;congregate at banks&lt;/a&gt; and places of business who have funded DAPL.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;We will demonstrate that we are united in democratic solidarity with all concerned citizens against the arbitrary will of corporate greed, according to our first amendment right.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have 65 days until Trump is inaugurated as President of the United States. We must use this time to make a difference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This Tuesday is the day to act.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Find a &lt;a href=&quot;https://actionnetwork.org/event_campaigns/nov-15-nodapl-day-of-action-at-army-corps-of-engineers&quot;&gt;location&lt;/a&gt; near you.
Find out more about Indigenous led &lt;a href=&quot;https://nodaplsolidarity.org/&quot;&gt;movement&lt;/a&gt; to stop the DAPL.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Katherine Sylwester and Garth Hughes-Odgers</name></author><summary type="html">The ongoing protest against the construction of the Dakota Access Pipeline (DAPL) has generated a great deal of press over the past few months. This Tuesday, November 15th, we, the outraged of the United States will demonstrate our nationwide solidarity with the people of the Standing Rock Sioux Tribe in opposition to this project.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/assets/images/posts/dapl-protest.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Bernie Sanders Endorses Keith Ellison for DNC Chair</title><link href="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/11/bernie-sanders-endorses-keith-ellison.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bernie Sanders Endorses Keith Ellison for DNC Chair" /><published>2016-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-11-11T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/11/bernie-sanders-endorses-keith-ellison</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/11/bernie-sanders-endorses-keith-ellison.html">&lt;p&gt;Today, Bernie Sanders has thrown his support behind Minnesota Representative Keith Ellison for Chairman of the Democratic National Convention. Rep. Ellison, the first Muslim elected to Congress, was an early and ardent supporter of Sanders’ presidential run during the Democratic Primary. As a co-chair of Bernie’s Congressional Progressive Caucus, the two have frequently worked together with other Democrats to introduce progressive legislation such as increasing the minimum wage and banning private prisons.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Keith Ellison opposes the TPP and has sponsored legislation that would stop corporations from storing their money in offshore tax havens. He understands that the current concentration of wealth has distorted our democracy and has eroded our country’s social and cultural fabric. He has voted to allow rehabilitated drug convicts to get student loans, to expunge criminal records for first time drug offenders after probation, and has voted NO on more funding for Mexico to fight the failed drug war. Rep. Ellison has also stood in solidarity with the protestors against the North Dakota Access Pipeline when others have remained silent. Keith understood that a populist wave would be sweeping throughout the nation and that a Trump presidency was possible, saying so back in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FHkPadFK34o&quot;&gt;July 2015&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role of the Democratic National Committee is not a small one. It coordinates and funds candidates throughout the country for local, state, and federal office and is responsible for developing the party platform. In the future, we need progressive Democrats to run in all elections, from school boards in California to Senate races in Wyoming. The American people need to be exposed to a new Democratic Party, a party that has thrown away the shackles of big donors and lobbyists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is why we must join Bernie Sanders in promoting Representative Keith Ellison. The current leadership of the Democratic Party can no longer afford to ignore our progressive agenda. Ellison understands that Trump tapped into the insecurity and unfairness that many Americans are feeling today. He knows that if Democrats wish to win back seats from Republicans, they need to return to defending trade unions, reverse the decline in working-class wages, and take care of the American people whose livelihoods have been lost to free trade deals. We have already demonstrated that a grassroots movement, Bernie Sander’s Political Revolution, can go toe to toe against even the most well-oiled political machine. Rep. Ellison can help guide this Revolution, pave a path forward for the Democratic Party and restore control of our democracy to the American people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, if we wish to exert our influence, we must do so quickly. Nancy Pelosi, the incoming House Minority Leader, is one of many who will be trying to get her choice picked as the new chair. We must not let the DNC pick another corporatist Democrat. We can do our part by &lt;a href=&quot;http://my.democrats.org/page/s/contact-the-democrats&quot;&gt;sending a message directly to the DNC&lt;/a&gt; and letting them know that we support Rep. Ellison. We can also contact Pelosi (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/NancyPelosi&quot;&gt;Facebook&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/nancypelosi&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/nancypelosi/&quot;&gt;Instagram&lt;/a&gt; / &lt;a href=&quot;https://pelosi.house.gov/contact-me/email-me&quot;&gt;Email&lt;/a&gt;) and assure her that we will not blindly follow her leadership choice out of party loyalty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lend your support by joining the Facebook Page: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/KeithForDNC/&quot;&gt;Keith For DNC&lt;/a&gt; and make your voice heard by signing the &lt;a href=&quot;http://pac.petitions.moveon.org/sign/appoint-keith-ellison?source=keithfordnc&amp;amp;fb_test=0&quot;&gt;petition&lt;/a&gt; to Appoint Keith Ellison as DNC Chair!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Harpreet Chima</name></author><summary type="html">Today, Bernie Sanders has thrown his support behind Minnesota Representative Keith Ellison for Chairman of the Democratic National Convention. Rep. Ellison, the first Muslim elected to Congress, was an early and ardent supporter of Sanders’ presidential run during the Democratic Primary. As a co-chair of Bernie’s Congressional Progressive Caucus, the two have frequently worked together with other Democrats to introduce progressive legislation such as increasing the minimum wage and banning private prisons.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/assets/images/posts/Keith_Ellison_01.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">On the Results of the 2016 Election</title><link href="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/10/election-results-statement.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On the Results of the 2016 Election" /><published>2016-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-11-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/10/election-results-statement</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/10/election-results-statement.html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Fellow Americans,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night’s election is a somber reminder for the progressive movement in the United States: progress is not a guarantee.  The executive branch is now completely under Republican control and many of our down-ballot hopefuls were unsuccessful. Despite these setbacks, we must continue fighting for a brighter future for all Americans, no matter how long it takes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now is &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; the time to lose hope. Now is not the time to give up on the American Dream, nor to resign ourselves to four years of stagnation and regression. We must recognize the power that comes from our collective outrage. We must continue to use our power to energize, protest, and act with vigor towards progressive change. Now is the time to stand together boldly and say &lt;strong&gt;“Enough is Enough!”&lt;/strong&gt; We must stand together with our allies in the face of this new adversity and proclaim that we will &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; be silenced. We will &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; allow all the progress we have made so far to be undone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our fight for change in the 2018 midterm elections and the 2020 presidential elections begins today. We will influence our representatives through petitions and by phone and letter writing campaigns. We will get involved in local politics to find candidates who represent our message. We will take advantage of the next two years and be ready for the next election. Most importantly, we will never lose faith in the movement that Bernie Sanders started and we will continue to forge a path forward for The Political Revolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even now, we can look at November 8th and chalk up &lt;a href=&quot;https://ourrevolution.com/election-2016/&quot;&gt;dozens of wins&lt;/a&gt; for Bernie-endorsed candidates!  It is now up to us to move past the disappointment of the election results and begin our fight a new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To that end, it is crucial that we do not let our anger and spite stand in the way of our ultimate goals. We must trust those who stand with us, and we must work to make allies of our enemies. This election has shown just how divided Americans are, but no matter our personal grievances, no one is a lost cause. We will find common ground, and from that ground we will build a new era of American politics.
	Please help us by &lt;a href=&quot;http://polrevvols.herokuapp.com/&quot;&gt;joining our volunteer troops&lt;/a&gt; today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Solidarity,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Political Revolution&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>The Political Revolution</name></author><summary type="html">Dear Fellow Americans,</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://politicalrev.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/assets/images/posts/tpr-logo-vertical.png" /></entry></feed>
