<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://smona.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://smona.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://smona.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2016-11-10T03:53:03+00:00</updated><id>http://smona.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org//</id><subtitle>We can change the future of America, but we need your help.</subtitle><author><name>{&quot;twitter&quot;=&gt;&quot;@OurPoliticalRev&quot;}</name></author><entry><title type="html">On the Results of the 2016 Election</title><link href="http://smona.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/09/election-results-statement.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="On the Results of the 2016 Election" /><published>2016-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2016-11-09T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>http://smona.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/09/election-results-statement</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://smona.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/2016/11/09/election-results-statement.html">&lt;p&gt;Dear Fellow Americans,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last night’s election is a somber reminder for the progressive movement in the United States: progress is not a guarantee.  The executive branch is now completely under Republican control and many of our down-ballot hopefuls were unsuccessful. Despite these setbacks, we must continue fighting for a brighter future for all Americans, no matter how long it takes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now is &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; the time to lose hope. Now is not the time to give up on the American Dream, nor to resign ourselves to four years of stagnation and regression. We must recognize the power that comes from our collective outrage. We must continue to use our power to energize, protest, and act with vigor towards progressive change. Now is the time to stand together boldly and say &lt;strong&gt;“Enough is Enough!”&lt;/strong&gt; We must stand together with our allies in the face of this new adversity and proclaim that we will &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; be silenced. We will &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; allow all the progress we have made so far to be undone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our fight for change in the 2018 midterm elections and the 2020 presidential elections begins today. We will influence our representatives through petitions and by phone and letter writing campaigns. We will get involved in local politics to find candidates who represent our message. We will take advantage of the next two years and be ready for the next election. Most importantly, we will never lose faith in the movement that Bernie Sanders started and we will continue to forge a path forward for The Political Revolution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even now, we can look at November 8th and chalk up &lt;a href=&quot;https://ourrevolution.com/election-2016/&quot;&gt;dozens of wins&lt;/a&gt; for Bernie-endorsed candidates!  It is now up to us to move past the disappointment of the election results and begin our fight a new.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To that end, it is crucial that we do not let our anger and spite stand in the way of our ultimate goals. We must trust those who stand with us, and we must work to make allies of our enemies. This election has shown just how divided Americans are, but no matter our personal grievances, no one is a lost cause. We will find common ground, and from that ground we will build a new era of American politics.
	Please help us by &lt;a href=&quot;http://polrevvols.herokuapp.com/&quot;&gt;joining our volunteer troops&lt;/a&gt; today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Solidarity,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Political Revolution&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>The Political Revolution</name></author><summary type="html">Dear Fellow Americans,</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://smona.github.io/thepoliticalrev.org/assets/images/american-flag.jpg" /></entry></feed>
